(Mrs Cooper:)You know, we have an Indian gentleman
at our church.
(Mrs Cooper:)A Dr. Patel. It's a beautiful story.
(Mrs Cooper:)The Lord spoke to him and moved him
to give us all 20 percent off on LASEK.
(Mrs Cooper:)You know, those that needed it.
(Leonard:)That is a lovely story.
Are we gonna do anything
about Sheldon?
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, we will.
You have to take your time with Sheldon.
His father, God rest his soul, used to say:
"Mary, you have to take your time
with Sheldon."
- Sounds like a wise man.
- Oh, not so wise.
He once tried to fight a bobcat
for some licorice.
(Mrs Cooper:)So everybody grab a plate
and a pretty placemat that Shelly wove.
(Penny:)Has Shelly ever freaked out
like this before?
(Mrs Cooper:)Oh, all the time.
(Mrs Cooper:)I remember one summer
when he was 13...
(Mrs Cooper:)...he built a small nuclear reactor
in the shed...
...and told everybody he was gonna provide
electricity for the town.
(Mrs Cooper:)Well, the only problem was, he had no,
what you call, fissionable materials.